OLARINDE MUTALIBI OLAYEMI

Contact Address: 5, Ifeolu Street, Alakia airport, Ibadan. Email Address: olayemiolarinde86@gmail.com Mobile No+2347039254748, +2348160452242

PROFILE

Due to some challenges facing the industrial and production sector, science and technology, I was able to specialize in engineering majorly on power and machinery operations, safety and maintenance of machines with proficiency in MS word, excel, Autocadetc.

OBJECTIVES

- To work effectively and efficiently to achieve set of goals.
- To work under pressure and any other conditions.
- To work in team.
- To implement marketing and entrepreneurial skills.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth: 23rd April, 1986

Marital Status: Single

Nationality: Nigerian

State of Origin: Osun

L.G.A: Isokan

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

•	B.Sc. (Agricultural and Environmental Engineering),	2016
	University of Ibadan, Ibadan	
•	H.N.D. in Agricultural Engineering,	
	Federal College of Agriculture, Moor Plantation, Ibadan.	2012
•	N.D Agricultural Engineering	
	Federal; College of Agriculture, Moor Plantation, Ibadan.	2009
•	N.E.C.O	
•	W.A.S.S.C.E	

OTHER QUALIFICATION(S)

•	Certificate on fish farming	2013
•	Certificate of NDLEA membership	2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

 Nigerian Railway Corporation, Dugbe, Ibadan (Casual Staff) Federal College of Agriculture Akure (N.Y.S.C), (Practical Instructor) 	2014-2016 2013-2014
 Feedback Computers, Akure (Computer Operator) Arvee Industries Limited, Sango-Otta (Quality Control Officer) 	2013-2014 2009-2010
 Alamit Industries Limited (Fabricator) Motiss Table Water 	2008-2009
(Machines Operator)Paraclect Medical Laboratory	2005-2006
(Laboratory Technician) • Bola Farms	2003-2005
(Farm Manager)	2001-2003

THESIS

•	Construction and Performance Evaluation of a Palm-nut Fiber Separator,	2012
•	Construction of an Office Cabinet	2009

HOBBIES: Writing, Reading, Research, Football.

REFEREES:

• Engr. (Dr) A. O Adejumo

Head, Agricultural Engineering Department, Federal College of Agriculture, Ibadan.

Tel: +238076559099

• Engr. B.O Afolabi

Head, Machine operation and maintenance sector,

Federal College of Agriculture, Ibadan.

Tel: +2348073242515

• Engr. Ilori T.A

Head, Welding and Fabrication Agricultural Engineering, Department, Federal College of Agriculture, Ibadan.

Tel: +2348033549356